Atlantic States Legal Foundation; Records apap311
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1966-2009; Undated; 2; 47.82 cu. ft.
  - General Publications, ca. 1966-2009; Undated; 2.4
    - Chesapeake Shoreline Erosion Study, Progress Report No. 2, 1985 June (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 4-5)
    - Chronic Toxicity of Copper to the Fathead Minnow (Pimephales promelas) in Soft Water, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Citizens' Guide to Combined Sewer Overflows in the City of Detroit, 1990 December (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - A Citizen's Guide to the Detroit River Remedial Action Plan, Undated (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - A Citizen's Toxic Waste Audit Manual, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - City Care: A National Conference on the Urban Environment, 1979 April (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Clean Air Standards Attainment Act of 1987, 1988 June (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Clean Lakes, Clean Steel, 1995 December (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Clean Water: A Bargain at Any Cost, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Clean Water Clear Choice, 2001 August (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Clean Water Act Section 303(d) List: Illinois' Submittal for 1998, 1998 April (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Cleaning Up Contaminated Sediment, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Coal and its Interaction with Oxygen, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Coastal Barrier Resources System Draft Report to Congress, 1985 April (Oversized 8)
    - Coastal Storm Hazard Mitigation, Atlantic County Barrier Islands and Ocean City, New Jersey, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 2000 Water Quality Assessment 305(b) Report, 2000 April (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia Coastal Resources Management Program and Final Environmental Impact Statement, Vol. I, 1986 July (Oversized 8)
    - Communities Using the Law to Combat Environmental Racism, Draft, 1996 March (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Community Guide to Title V Clean Air Act Permits, 1997 June (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Conference of Park Superintendents, National Park Service, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Conference on the Coastal Bays of Maryland and Virginia, 1981 April (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Conservation Districts and Great Lakes Water Quality: Present and Prospective Roles, 1990 October (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Constructing the Natural: The Darker Side of the Environmental Movement, 1985 March (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Containment Issues of Concern, National Wildlife Refuges, 1986 April (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Creating an Analytical and Regulatory Framework to Address Great Lakes Air Toxics Deposition, Undated (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 27)
    - The Crisis of Wildlife Habitat in Illinois Today, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Decline of Submerged Aquatic Plants in Chesapeake Bay, 1979 July (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Delaware Coastal Management Program and Final Environmental Impact Statement, Vol. I, 1980 March (Oversized 8)
    - The Delaware Estuary, Discover its Secrets, 1995 January (Oversized 9)
    - The Delaware Estuary, Discover its Secrets, Executive Summary of the Delaware Estuary Management Plan, 1994 December (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Delaware National Estuarine Research Reserve, Final Environmental Impact Statement / Draft Management Plan, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Department of the Interior, Final Environmental Statement, Nationwide Outdoor Recreation Plan, 1973 December (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Developing Regulatory Programs for the Control of Acid Precipitation, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Development and Verification of Numerical Models for Predicting the Initial Fate of Dredged Material Disposed in Open Water, Report 1, 1993 May (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 34)
    - The Development Document for the Effluent Monitoring Regulation for the Pulp and Paper Sector, 1989 July (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Directory of New Jersey Environmental Risk Education Efforts, 1988 December (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Directory of Pollution Prevention Funding Organizations, 1994 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Disasters in Water Development II, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Dispersion Analysis of Charleston, South Carolina, Ocean Dredged Material Disposal Site, 1994 March (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 39)
    - The Do's and Don'ts of Home Insulation, 1981 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 40)
    - Down the Drain: Toxic Pollution and the Status of Retreatment in Rhode Island, 1986 September (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 41)
    - Draft Environmental Report on Proposed Exploratory Drilling Offshore North Carolina, Volume I, 1989 November (Oversized 9)
    - Dredge Plant Equipment and Systems Processes; Summary Report for Technical Area 3, 1995 November (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - The Dynamic Duo: RCRA and SARA Title III, 1989 June (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - The Ecology of Tijuana Estuary, Undated (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - The Ecological Role of Fire in Sierran Conifer Forests, 1973 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Economic Analysis: Converting from Petroleum-Based to Ultraviolet-Light Cured Coating System for Medium-Size Wood Products Manufacturers, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - The Effect of Federal Water Projects on Cultural Resources, 1977 September (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - The Effect of Methylmercuric Chloride, Cadmium Chloride, and Lead Nitrate on Six Biochemical Factors of the Brook Trout, 1977 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Effects of Aroclor® 1248 and 1260 on the Fathead Minnow, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - The Effects of Household Sanitary Systems on Effluent Phosphate Levels, Research Report No. 2, 1973 March (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Effects of Pollution on Freshwater Fish, 1978 June (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Electronics Industry Casebook, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Elemental Marking of Arthropod Pests in Agricultural Systems, 1991 June (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Emerging Links Between Chronic Disease and Environmental Exposure: Parkinson's Disease, 2003 May (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Empress II Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1984-1985 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 14-15)
    - Endangered and Threatened Species of Pennsylvania, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Energy and Environmental Profile of the U.S. Iron and Steel Industry, 1996 July (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Environment and Health in Louisiana: The Cancer Problem, 1984 March (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 18)
    - The Environment and Health in Louisiana: The Cancer Problem, Executive Summary, 1984 March (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Environmental Influences on Breast Cancer Risk, 1997 May-1997 June (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Environmental Justice Strategy: Executive Order 12898, 1995 April (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Environmental Steel, Undated (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Environmental Training Resources Catalog for Small Communities, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Established Projects for Coastal Protection Master Plan, 1986 January (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 24)
    - The Establishment of the River Restoration Centre, Forward Plan, 1997 November (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Evaluation of Solidification / Stabilization Technology for Buffalo River Sediment, 1991 May (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - ETA Glossary of Program Terms and Definitions, Second Edition, 1979 November (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 27)
    - European Dredging Industry Overview with Emphasis on Geotechnical Descriptors, 1993 August (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Evaluation of the Urban Homesteading Demonstration Program, Second Annual Report, 1978 September (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Everybody's Problem: Hazardous Waste, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Fertility on the Brink: The Legacy of the Chemical Age, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Final Environment Impact Statement Elkhorn Slough Estuarine Sanctuary, Undated (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Final Environment Impact Statement, Empress II, 1988 April (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Final Environment Impact Statement for the Designation of Ocean Dredged Material Disposal Sites for Arecibo, Mayaquez, Ponce, and Yabucoa, Puerto Rico, 1988 May (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Final Guidance for Implementation of Requirements Under Section 304(1) of the Clean Water Act as Amended, 1988 March (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Final Recommendations on the Management of the National Wildlife Refuge System, 1979 April (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Final Recovery Plan for the Humpback Whale, 1991 November (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Fish and Offshore Oil Development, Undated (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Fool's Wisdom: An Analysis of the Anti-Conservation Movement in the Midwest, Undated (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Forty Ways to Make Government Purchasing Green, 1992 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - A Forum for Environmental Solutions, 1986-1987 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - GATT: The Environment and the Third World, A Resource Guide, Undated (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Geochemistry of Recent Lake Michigan Sediments, 1981 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Geotechnical Factors in the Dredgeability of Sediments, Report I, 1993 November (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Geotechnical Factors in the Dredgeability of Sediments, Report 2-3, 1993 October (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Getting the Most from Out Materials: Making New Jersey the State of the Art, 1991 June (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Getting the Most from Out Materials: Strategies from the New Jersey Conference, 1991 June (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Global Warming and Energy Priorities: A National Perspective, 1989 November (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - The Great Lakes Ecosystem Protection Agenda, ca. 1992 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Great Lakes Environmental Research Laboratory, Annual Report, 1985-1985 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Green Products by Design, 1992 October (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Greenhouse Effect and Sea Level Rise, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Greening the Garden State, 2000 April (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Groundwater: Indiana's Unseen Resource, 1987 March (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Guidance Manual for the Integrated Exposure Uptake Biokinetic Model for Lead in Children, 1994 February (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 16)
    - A Guide to Citizens Law Enforcement, 1996 May (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Guide to Products Services, National Small Flows Clearinghouse, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Guidelines for State Historic Preservation Legislation, 1972 March (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Guidelines for Wetlands Management in Ontario, Undated (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 20)
    - The Gulf of Maine, Action Plan, 1991 July (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Handbook of Federal Systems and Services for Marine Pollution Data and Information, 1985 June (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Hazardous Waste Report, Instructions and Forms, 1989 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Heavy Metals in Agricultural Lands Receiving Chemical Sewage Sludges, 1973 March (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Helpful Hints for Analyzing Volatile Organics, Undated (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - High Speed Rail Compact, 1989 May (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Higher Ground, 1998 July (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Hoosier Landscape, Undated (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Hormone Copycats, 1994 April (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Hydraulically Transported Clay Balls, 1994 April (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Identification and Distribution of Inorganic Components in Water: What to Measure?, 1977 September (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Illinois Natural History Survey, 2003 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 32)
    - The Impact of Factory Farming in Franklin County Vermont, Undated (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 33)
    - The Impact of Hurricane David on the Forests of Dominica, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Impacts of Near-Bottom Currents on Dredged Material Mounds Near Mobile Bay, 1995 July (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Impacts of Nutrients on the Potomac Estuary, 1979 December (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Impacts of Coastal Energy Development on New Jersey's Shorefront Recreational Resources, 1984 March (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Improvements to the Automated Real-Time Tidal Elevation System, 1993 October (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Improving Wetland Public Outreach, Training and Education, and Interpretation, ca. 1993 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 39)
    - In Harm's Way: Toxic Threats to Child Development, 2000; Undated (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - In the Drink: Illinois, 1995 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Incineration in Hazardous Waste Management, 1975 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Industrial Waste Reduction: State Policy Options, 1990 November (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Information Summary, Area of Concern: Ashtabula River, Ohio, 1990 December (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Information Summary, Area of Concern: Sheboygan River, Wisconsin, 1991 March (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Inland Waterways: Proceedings of a National Workshop on the Beneficial Uses of Dredged Material, 1988 November (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Integrated Pest Management in the Great Lakes Basin Ecosystem, 1990 June (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Interaction of Chemical Pollutants and Virus in a Crustacean: A Novel Bioassay System, 1977 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - International Coastal Cleanup Overview, 1991 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - International Coastal Cleanup Results, 1991 (Oversized 10)
    - International Joint Commission, United States and Canada, Activities Report, 1986 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Introduced Species in U.S. Coastal Waters, 2001 October (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Introduction to a Discussion of the Use of Aquatic Toxicity Tests for Evaluation of the Effects of Toxic Substances, 1978 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Inventory of Non-Federally Funded Marine Pollution Research, Development and Monitoring Activities, 1984 November (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Investigating Human Exposure to Contaminants in the Environment, Draft, ca. 1994 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Investigation of Real-Time Differential Global Positioning System (DGPS) Data Link Alternatives, 1992 December (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Jean Lafitte National Historical Park, Draft General Management Plan, Development Concept Plan, Environmental Assessment Plan, 1981 July (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Jean Lafitte National Historical Park, Draft/Land Protection Plan, Undated (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Jean Lafitte National Historical Park, General Management Plan, Development Concept Plan, 1982 July (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Just Add Water: Violations of Federal Health Standards in Tap Water, 1996 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Landscaping Around Home, 1982 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Lake Carriers' Association, 1993 Annual Report, 1994 Objectives, ca. 1994 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Lake Pontchartrain, Louisiana and Vicinity Hurricane Protection Project Reevaluation Study, Volume I, 1984 July (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Lake Pontchartrain, Louisiana and Vicinity Hurricane Protection Project Reevaluation Study, Volume III, 1984 July (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Lake Superior Binational Program, State of the Lake Superior Basin Reporting Series, Vol. II, 1993 October (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Land Application of Sewage Sludge, 1972 September (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Lands Directorate, No. 25, Methods of Preserving Wildlife Habitat, 1983 March (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Lead, Annual Report, U.S. Department of the Interior, 1991 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Lead-Based Paint Hazards, 1994 July (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Lead in Drinking Water, 1993 October (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Leasing Energy Resources on the Outer Continental Shelf, 1987 July (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 31)
    - A Legislative History of the Superfund Amendments and Reauthorization Act of 1986, 1990 October (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Louisiana Water Pollution Control Regulations, Second Draft, 1984 December (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Lowell, Massachusetts: Report of the Lowell Historic Canal District Commission to the Ninety Fifth Congress…, 1977 January (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - LTFATE: A Model to Investigate the Long-Term Fate and Stability of Dredged Material Disposal Sites; User's Guide, 1995 May (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - The Maine Guide to Mussel Raft Culture, 1999 September (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Making Cities Green, A Funding Guide for the Urban Environment, 1980 November (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Management Policies, National Park Service, 1978 (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Managing Mobility, Report of the American Public Transit Association Transit 2000 Task Force, 1989 November (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Manual on Public Involvement in Environmental Assessment, 1988 (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Manufacturing from Recyclables, 1995 February (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Massachusetts Barrier Beaches, Undated (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Mining Conservation Directory, 1998 June (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Money Saving Tips for Home Appliances, 1980 (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Monitoring of Selected Trace Organics During Biological Wastewater Treatment, 1982 February (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Narragansett Bay: Issues, Resources, Status, and Management, 1987 August (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 13)
    - National Estuarine Inventory, 1968 (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 14)
    - National Food Security Act Manual, 1994 (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 15-18)
    - National Grid Transco, Annual Report and Accounts, 2002-2003 (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - National Marine Pollution Program Summary of Federal Programs and Projects, FY 1985 Updated, 1986 December (Oversized 10)
    - National Marine Pollution Program Summary of Federal Programs and Projects, FY 1986 Updated, 1987 November (Oversized 11)
    - National Park Concessions, 1948 (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Nature's Way: How Wastewater Treatment Works for You, 1985 (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Navigation: The Role of the Corps, 1983 October (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 22)
    - The New Approach: Integrating Transportation and Development in the National Capital Region, 1992 November (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 23)
    - No Net Loss and The Role of Restoration and Creation, 1990 April (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Nonpoint Source Pollution Assessment of the Lower Susquehanna River Basin, 1977 November (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - NOAA's National Ocean Service, Accomplishments, 2006 (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Notification, Testing, and Control of Chemicals: Major National and International Issues, Draft, 1980 May (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Ocean Incineration, Undated (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 28)
    - One People, One Planet, 1995 Rural Coalition Annual Assembly, 1995 June (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Oil Spills and the Marine Environment, 1974 (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Operations Manual for a Local Landowner Program, 1971 April (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Pacific Salmon and Artificial Propagation under the Endangered Species Act, 1992 October (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Pacific Salmon and Steelhead: Potential Impacts of Endangered Species Act Listings, 1991 March (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Patuxent River Policy Plan, 1984 January (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Peer Review, Standards for the Disposal of Sewage Sludge, 1993 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
    - The Phantom of Fiddler Creek, 1986 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Platting Wastewater Treatment System, 1988 June (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 6-9)
    - Pollution Prevention Directory, 1994 September (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Pollution Prevention in California, 1992 July (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Pollution Prevention Opportunities in Agriculture, 1994 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Pollution Prevention Opportunities in Oil and Gas Production Drilling and Exploration, 1993 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Pollution Prevention Opportunities in the Fish Processing Industry, 1993 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Pollution Prevention Opportunities in the Forestry and Sulfite Pulp Processing Industries, 1993 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Polychlorinated Biphenyls in Four Freshwater Fish Species from the Willamette River, Oregon, Undated (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Population Studies of Mines and Mineral Processing Sites, 1997 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Preliminary Design for Dredged Material Placement Physical Modeling Facilities, 1992 December (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 18)
    - A Prescription for Healthy Great Lakes, 1991 February (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Proceeds of the Workshop on Cause-Effect Linkages, International Join Commission, Council of Great Lakes Research Managers, 1989 March (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 20)
    - The Product is the Poison, 1991 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - A Proposed Air Resources Board Regarding Incineration as an Acceptable Technology for PCB Disposal, 1981 March (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Protect Your Family From Lead in Your Home, 1995 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Protecting Your Housing Investment, 1980 October (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Protecting Floodplain Resources, 1996 June (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - The Protection of Indiana's Ground Water, Strategy and Draft Implementation Plan, Undated (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Providing for Your Heirs-Non-Sale Property Transfers, 1981 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Provincially and Regionally Significant Wetlands in Southern Ontario Interim Report, 1987 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 28)
    - The Public Benefits of Cleaned Water: Emerging Greenway Opportunities, 1977 August (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Public Involvement in the U.S. Forest Service Roadless-area Review, 1977 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 30)